

VISHWADEEP SINGH KUSHWAHA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I believe that there is always a room for improvements regardless of one's level of expertise. These improvements can only be brought by trying new things and making mistakes while doing it. Learning from mistakes and having a positive attitude is the key to growth. I am also a technology believer and I believe that a better place for everyone can be achieved with advancements in tech.

SKILLS

Front-End

React, Gatsby, MUI, Tailwind, GSAP, GraphQL, Vue

Back-End

NodeJS, NestJS, Express, Postgres, MongoDB, CosmosDB, AuthO, Keycloak, Azure Functions, Netlify Functions

Tools & Platforms

Azure DevOps, Azure Blob Storage, Keycloak, Docker, Kubernetics, Google Maps and Images API, Keyvault

HOBBIES

Cycling, Books, Gaming, History, Physics

EDUCATION

LOVELY PROFESSIONAL UNIVERSITY

2014- 2016 | Bachelor's In Technology(Dropped)

SDA HIGH SCHOOL

2012-2014 | High School

EXPERIENCE

2022 SLEEKSKY - Software developer (Aug 2022 - Present) NestJS, React, Express, Azure, Keycloak

- I am responsible for building robust backend and frontend using react, node, nest.js and technologies around it.
- While at Sleeksky, I worked on a CMS, adding payment feature and a json visual form editor; and on a University-Hospital-Student placement management application.

2020 FLOCKALONG - Web developer (Dec 2020 - Aug 2022) Gatsby, Nodejs, Netlify Functions, C#, AuthO, Google Maps, Algolia, Cypress

- I was responsible for developing Gatsby based Front-End which served as a platform for customers to create, join and manage trips.
- Developed and deployed Back-End on Azure to facilitate the front-end.
- Implemented Algolia search engine and automated data updating to Algolia servers.

2019 KHAOBAO - Operations Manager (Dec 2018 - Nov 2019) Java, Android, Javascript

- I was responsible for development of Android Apps -Customer Side and Delivery Guy app.
- In parallel I was handling day to day operations including signing new restaurants, improving customer experience and launching new services.
- Completed 40k successful orders over a period of more than 14 months.

CONTACT

78140 92325 mailvishwadeephere@gmail.com

PROJECTS (FREELANCING)

2022 TARGET DELIVERY(Aug 2022) Logistics for MSMEs

- A bare minimum application for admin, driver and client to allow the company to take and manage order.
- Develop whole business model from defining core values to contemplating cost and distribution.

2019 GBC (June 2019 - July 2019)

Linux and Windows Machine Scripting, Node

- I was responsible for adding local windows machine as an option to run shell scripts on an existing Node based interface(UI was based on Bootstrap).
- · Was responsible for logging results from Linux and Windows Machines using socket.io
- Additional minor bugs fixing to run scripts on Linux machines.

2018 FRIENDLY ROOTS (December 2018 - January 2019) Javascript, Html, Node, CSS

- A Shopify commerce website to showcase all products.
- Major customization to existing theme because obviously, it was a theme.
- Integrate Affiliation part to the theme i.e.; Spin wheel, Lucky draw and Referral Affiliation.